export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "Haus" mean in English?',
      choices: ['House', 'Car', 'Tree', 'Book'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'House',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Danke" in English?',
      choices: ['Please', 'Sorry', 'Thank you', 'Excuse me'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Thank you',
    },
    {
      question: 'What color is "Blau" in English?',
      choices: ['Red', 'Blue', 'Yellow', 'Green'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Blue',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the capital of Germany?',
      choices: ['Munich', 'Berlin', 'Hamburg', 'Frankfurt'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Berlin',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the day before "Mittwoch"?',
      choices: ['Montag', 'Dienstag', 'Donnerstag', 'Freitag'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Dienstag',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the english word for "Apfel"?',
      choices: ['Apple', 'Banana', 'Orange', 'Strawberry'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Apple',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the author of "Die Leiden des jungen Werthers"?',
      choices: ['Johann Wolfgang von Goethe', 'Friedrich Schiller', 'Thomas Mann', 'Hermann Hesse'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Johann Wolfgang von Goethe',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Guten Tag" in English?',
      choices: ['Goodbye', 'Good morning', 'Good evening', 'Good night'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Good morning',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the German term for "Tisch"?',
      choices: ['Table', 'Chair', 'Bed', 'Lamp'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Table',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Schule" in English?',
      choices: ['School', 'Hospital', 'Bank', 'Library'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'School',
    },
  ],
}